[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Steel Magnolias was released in 1987.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who of the following is not a member of the 1980s Brat Pack?", "correct_answer": "Jennifer Jason-Leigh", "incorrect_answers": ["Molly Ringwald", "Ally Sheedy", "Demi Moore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Napoleon Dynamite, Napoleon\u2019s brother Kip tells Napoleon that he is training to be what?", "correct_answer": "Cage fighter", "incorrect_answers": ["Street fighter", "Professional wrestler", "Ninja"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine?", "correct_answer": "Dionysus", "incorrect_answers": ["Hermes", "Hephaestus", "Zeus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What powers do we know for sure that Tim from Monty Python and the Holy Grail possesses?", "correct_answer": "The power to conjure fire and teleport", "incorrect_answers": ["The power to curdle milk from fifty farthings away", "The power to summon wind and rain", "The power to hypnotise small, furry creatures, and speak with animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main ingredient in the Chinese meal called Lions head ?", "correct_answer": "Pork meatballs", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabbage", "Lions testicles", "Shrimp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take light to travel from the Sun to the Earth?", "correct_answer": "About 8 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["Less than 1 minute", "Just over 34 minutes", "It arrives instantaneously"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who crucifies Jesus in the 2004 movie The Passion of the Christ?", "correct_answer": "Mel Gibson", "incorrect_answers": ["A movie extra", "Francesco DeVito, who plays Peter", "Luca Lionello, who plays Judas Iscariot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these couples is wed at the end of the movie Journey to the Center of the Earth?", "correct_answer": "Alec McEwen and Jenny", "incorrect_answers": ["Oliver S. Lindenbrook and Claire Burke", "The Laird of Glendarach and  Rose Weir", "Guide Hans Belke and Sigrid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Patty Loveless performed the song On Down Line for the Black Dog soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sport is rated as the most popular sport among Egyptians?", "correct_answer": "Football (soccer)", "incorrect_answers": ["Baseball", "Handball", "Tennis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If they call me a newbie then I am new to the Internet; and/or new to the subject in general.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]